krishnvaibhav2003@gmail.com +91 8075961210 Kochi / Delhi <u>Linkedin</u>

# R KRISHN VAIBHAV

### DEVELOPER

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Department Portal**

- Implemented and maintained key features of Department portal, including chat system and search engine
- Provided access to announcements, marks, and timetable for tracking academic progress
- Project Available At https://github.com/krishnvaibhav/University\_portal

#### **Transcribers**

- Project goal is to provide a free website that can convert any audio file, in any language supported by speech recognition API, into text
- · Audio files are accepted as input to the website
- · Website can convert audio into text in any language

#### Unibuddies

- Created dynamic React Native app for pre-university connections
- Implemented personalized algorithms for matching based on origin and interests
- Established a public forum to facilitate discussion and content sharing
- Project Available At https://github.com/krishnvaibhav/Unibuddies

#### TOP SKILLS

PYTHON
REACT JS
REACT NATIVE
HTML AND CSS
JAVASCRIPT
MYSQL
FLUTTER

#### CERTIFICATION

- · Foundation of Cyber Security
- Machine Learning Skillvertex
- The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 2022
- The Complete JavaScript Course 2022: From Zero to Expert!
- · Flutter and Dart 2024 Edition
- Supervised Machine Learning: Regression And Classification

#### PROFILE

I'm a passionate student with a love for coding and technology. I've garnered experience in various coding projects and am committed to expanding my knowledge, particularly in cyber security, to make a positive impact in the tech industry.

#### EDUCATION

# Christ (Deemed To Be) University, Delhi NCR, Bachelors in Computer Application

2021 - 2024

Graduated with cgpa of 3.65 / 4

## Bhavans Vidya Mandir Elamakkara, High School

2019 - 2021

- Completed high school education with a focus on Commerce and Informatics Practice
- Achieved a total score of 93.8% in Board Exams

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Mobile Developer Intern at MariApps

01/2024 - 4/2024

I contributed to the development of the Eyesea mobile application, a non-profit initiative empowering users to combat marine pollution. This project provided a valuable opportunity to apply my coding skills while supporting a cause I deeply care about.

#### Technical Team Lead at Upedian

03/2023 - 05/2023

- Lead developer responsible for developing the backend function of transcribers and image to text features.
- Designed web pages and increased user experience (UX) through JavaScript.
- Conducted recruitment through an interview process to hire skilled developers.

# Full Stack Developer Intern at Ambimed Healthcare

01/2023 - 04/2023

- Developed a user-friendly website using ReactJS
- Developed a driver app using React Native
- Implemented seamless booking, cancellation, and various other features

#### Machine Learning Trainee at Skill Vertex

07/2022 - 08/2022

- Completed 2 projects, major and minor, focused on data preparation, feature engineering, and ML algorithms
- Developed skills and gained hands-on experience in applying ML techniques to real-world problems